Inventory to the Annelise Graebner Anderson Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Office of Management and Budget, 1981-1983 (Box 28-139)
  - Cabinet Council Minutes – Legal Policy (Box-folder 116: 32)
  - Issue Alert: The Export Trading Company Act of 1982 Unemployment (Box-folder 116: 33)
  - Draft Annual Report on the Trade Agreements Program (Part II) (Box-folder 116: 34)
  - Committee on Public Works and Transportation – October 4, 1982 (Box-folder 116: 35)
  - Data on Aviation Accidents (Box-folder 116: 36)
  - Juvenile Justice and Delinquency Prevention Programs; A Background Paper (Box-folder 116: 37)
  - Interest subsidy paper – July 19, 1982 (Box-folder 116: 38)
  - “Federalism Initiative” – Tentative Administration Decisions (Box-folder 116: 39)
  - Report of the Working Group on Federal Credit Policy (Box-folder 116: 40)
  - SEC Regulation of Newsletter Investment Advisers (Box-folder 116: 41)
  - April and May FSLIC Supervisory Actions, and March – April FSLIC Outlays (Box-folder 116: 42)
  - Businessweek article on estimates of housing starts through 1985 (Box-folder 116: 43)
  - Minutes of July 27th Meeting on Financial Institution Reform (Box-folder 116: 44)
  - Learning Curve Strategy/Industry Sensitivity Analysis/Cooperative Consortium (Box-folder 116: 45)
  - Reactions From Ex-Im Meeting (Box-folder 116: 46)
  - Property/Barter (Box-folder 116: 47)
  - Zuch Task Force Recommendations on A-19 (Box-folder 116: 48)
  - Non-defense (Box-folder 117: 1)
  - Prospects for Enactment of the Immigration Legislation (Box-folder 117: 2)
  - Debt Problems of Less Developed Countries and U.S. Banks (Box-folder 117: 3)
  - Post Office (Box-folder 117: 4)
  - 1983 Budget Amendments for Mass Transit and Commuter Rail Transfer Assistance (Box-folder 117: 5)
  - Veto Message on Urgent Supplemental (Box-folder 117: 6)
  - A CBO study: Federal Housing Assistance: Alternative Approaches (Box-folder 117: 7)
  - War Risk (Box-folder 117: 8)
  - Response letter to the Washington Post article, “Reagan’s Ranking Couple” (Box-folder 117: 9)
  - Letter from Nick Stoer to Annelise Anderson (Box-folder 117: 10)
  - Letter from Nicholas N. Nardolillo (Box-folder 117: 11)
  - Letter from Dennis Bark (Box-folder 117: 12)
  - Invitation for Annelise Anderson to speak on March 11 to housing and construction industry executives (Box-folder 117: 13)
  - Center for the American Woman and Politics (CAWP) (Box-folder 117: 14)
  - Invitations (Box-folder 117: 15)
  - Speech Notes from Ed Dale (Box-folder 117: 16)
  - Transportation Systems Financing (Box-folder 117: 17)
  - Alice Rivlin Discussion (Box-folder 117: 18)
  - Eagleton Institute of Politics (Box-folder 117: 19)
  - Washington Semester Program-The American University – Economic Policy Semester (Box-folder 117: 20)
  - Theme of the forum (Box-folder 117: 21)
  - Program Notes (Box-folder 117: 22)
  - Biographical Data on Anthony Frank/Edward Ladd/Lila Petersen (Box-folder 117: 23)
  - Conference on Administering Immigration and Refugee Policies Sponsored by the German Marshall Fund of the United States (Box-folder 117: 24)
  - House Committee on Small Business (Box-folder 117: 25)
  - Rand Board of Trustees (Box-folder 117: 26)
  - Letter from Massoud Ahmadi about the presentation on “The OMB’s Perspective on Budgetary Process” (Box-folder 117: 27)
  - Letter from Jay Tontz about the Public Forum on October 20, 1982 (Box-folder 117: 28)
  - Letter from Richard Staar regarding OMB (Box-folder 117: 29)
  - Letter to Richard Evans regarding the National Committee Conference (Box-folder 117: 30)
  - Quick Turn-Around Exercise (Box-folder 117: 31)
  - General Electric Company Space Systems Division (Box-folder 117: 32)
  - Maritime Administration (Box-folder 117: 33)
  - Letter to Felice Schwartz from Annelise Anderson regarding the Catalyst dinner (Box-folder 117: 34)
  - Speech request for Washington State Transportation Center Conference at Lake Wilderness (Box-folder 117: 35)
  - Conrail (Box-folder 117: 36)
  - Talking Points Arguing Against “Alleghany-Mohawk” Airline Labor Protection Provisions (Box-folder 117: 37)
  - Weekly Activities Report – SDD/EG (Box-folder 117: 38)
  - Weekly Activities Reports (Box-folder 117: 39)
  - JTGM Weekly Activities Report (Box-folder 117: 40)
  - Electron Mail USPS (Box-folder 117: 41)
  - H.R. 2813 – Electronic Mail Act of 1981 (Box-folder 117: 42)
  - Postal Issues (Box-folder 117: 43)
  - USTTA (Box-folder 117: 44)
  - Venture Capital (Box-folder 117: 45)
  - Phase I Proposals of the Task Force on Violent Crime (Box-folder 117: 46)
  - Commerce, Science, and Transportation Committee (Box-folder 117: 47)
  - Interim Report, Housing Commission (Box-folder 117: 48)
  - Vouchers (Box-folder 117: 49)
  - Labor Protection Provision Attached to War Risk Insurance Bill (Box-folder 117: 50)
  - Modification of Section 408 of Airlines Deregulation Act (Box-folder 117: 51)
  - Legislative Problems Report (Box-folder 117: 52)
  - War Risk Insurance (Box-folder 117: 53)
  - Briefing Materials for Meeting with O’Donnell (Box-folder 117: 54)
  - Weekly Report on major negotiations – June 19, 1981 (Box-folder 117: 55)
  - BATF (Box-folder 118: 1)
  - Analyses, Fact Sheets and Explanatory Statements for the Upcoming House Floor Debate (Box-folder 118: 2)
  - Congressional Budget Committee Action on the First budget Resolution for 1982 (Box-folder 118: 3)
  - Reagan-Bipartisan (Box-folder 118: 4)
  - Background Material for Your Contribution to Floor Manager’s Statement (Box-folder 118: 5)
  - Comparisons of Administration’s, House Budget Committee (Jones) and Bipartisan (Latta-Gramm) Budget Proposals (Box-folder 118: 6)
  - Differences Between the Jones-House Budget Committee Alternative and the Reagan-Bipartisan Substitute (Box-folder 118: 7)
  - Function 850: General Purpose Fiscal Assistance (Box-folder 118: 8)
  - Function 750: Administration of Justice (Box-folder 118: 9)
  - Function 400: Transportation (Box-folder 118: 10)
  - Function 800: General Government (Box-folder 118: 11)
  - Function 370: Commerce and Housing Credit (Box-folder 118: 12)
  - Draft Statement for Cong. Latta (Box-folder 118: 13)
  - Bailouts (Box-folder 118: 14)
  - VCR Royalty Fees (Box-folder 118: 15)
  - 1981 Budget Control (Outside) (Box-folder 118: 16)
  - Weekly Activities Report—TCH Division (Box-folder 118: 17-18)
  - Miscellaneous opening notes (Box-folder 118: 19)
  - Border Agency (Box-folder 118: 20)
  - 1983 Budget (Box-folder 118: 21)
  - $220M in Additional 1982 Outlays (Box-folder 118: 22)
  - Reductions in 1982 New Commitments for Loan Guarantees (Box-folder 118: 23)
  - Summary Presentations of Dollar Changes and Program Implications – Agency FY 83-84 Ceiling Changes (Box-folder 118: 24)
  - Agency 1983-84 Budget (Box-folder 118: 25)
  - Budget Process (Box-folder 118: 26)
  - Justice-Prisons (Box-folder 119: 1)
  - Cabinet Council on Commerce and Trade (CCCT) (Box-folder 119: 2)
  - Membership – CCCT (Box-folder 119: 3)
  - CAB (Box-folder 119: 4-5)
  - Bus Regulatory (Box-folder 119: 6)
  - White House Staff Comments on 1983 Budget Decisions (Box-folder 119: 7)
  - 1982 September Request (Box-folder 119: 8)
  - Transportation (Box-folder 119: 9)
  - Indexing (Box-folder 119: 10)
  - Function 550: Health/Function 600: Income Security (Box-folder 119: 11)
  - State of the Union speech/fact sheet/talking points (Box-folder 119: 12)
  - Policy Guidance on Post-Reconciliation Act Budget Amendments (Box-folder 119: 13)
  - Resolution of Issues Related to Private Sector Transfer of Civil Land-Observing Satellite Activities (Box-folder 119: 14)
  - Out-of-cycle proposals (Box-folder 119: 15)
  - Reply to a letter from NARFE (Box-folder 119: 16)
  - Mass Transit Operating Subsidies (Box-folder 119: 17)
  - Senate Reconciliation Bill Floor Action (Box-folder 119: 18)
  - Utilization of Deobligated Funds (Box-folder 119: 19)
  - Budget Review Procedures (Box-folder 119: 20)
  - First Concurrent Resolution (Box-folder 119: 21)
  - Materials on the First Concurrent Resolution on the Budget for 1982 (Box-folder 119: 22)
  - Constitutional Balanced Budget Tax Limitation Amendment (Revised Draft) – March 16, 1982 (Box-folder 119: 23)
  - Budget Process (Box-folder 119: 24)
  - Budget Threats (Box-folder 119: 25)
  - Budget Review Board (Box-folder 119: 26)
  - New York Times article on data cuts (Box-folder 119: 27)
  - Coal Exports (Box-folder 119: 28)
  - Patent User Fees (Box-folder 119: 29)
  - GOES Satellite Reprogramming (Box-folder 119: 30)
  - NOAA (Box-folder 119: 31)
  - EDA Reprogramming (Box-folder 119: 32)
  - Seagrant/Commerce (Box-folder 119: 33)
  - Testimony on Breaux Bill – FYI (Box-folder 119: 34)
  - Enrolled Bill S. 304 – National Tourism Policy Act Sponsor – Sen. Pressler (R) South Dakota and 22 others (Box-folder 119: 35)
  - House Reconsideration of Exim Bank Funding (Box-folder 119: 36)
  - Appeal (Box-folder 119: 37)
  - Tourism (Box-folder 119: 38)
  - Governmentwide Statistical Consolidation (Box-folder 119: 39)
  - CSA Close-out Budget and 1982 Funding for FAADS and GDFF (Box-folder 119: 40)
  - Commerce (Box-folder 120: 1-3)
  - Oil Superfund Legislation and Coast Guard User Fees (Box-folder 120: 4)
  - CCCT on Coal Export Policy (Box-folder 120: 5)
  - Survey of Income and Program Participation (SIPP) (Box-folder 120: 6)
  - Crime (Box-folder 120: 7)
  - Very Rough Draft of Credit Controls Act Expiration Proposal (Box-folder 120: 8)
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting (CPB) (Box-folder 120: 9)
  - The President’s Meeting with the Farmers on February 6 (Box-folder 120: 10)
  - February 9 Meeting with State Legislators and County Officials (Box-folder 120: 11)
  - February 6 Meeting with Senate Republican Committee Chairmen (Box-folder 120: 12)
  - Advanced copy of Senate Budget Committee’s comments on budget reduction proposals (Box-folder 120: 13)
  - Miscellaneous notes (Box-folder 120: 14)
  - Enclosure to a letter to Senator Domenici (Box-folder 120: 15)
  - Senate Commerce, Science, and Transportation (Box-folder 120: 16)
  - Memo for the heads of Departments and agencies, economic recovery program (Box-folder 120: 17)
  - Support in the House for the President’s Economic Recovery Program (Box-folder 120: 18)
  - A and B Issues (Box-folder 120: 19)
  - Conrail (Box-folder 120: 20)
  - The Northwest Railroad Problem by George W. Hilton (Box-folder 120: 21)
  - Credit Initiative (Box-folder 120: 22)
  - Credit Exercise (Box-folder 120: 23)
  - Conrail (Box-folder 120: 24)
  - Conrail (Box-folder 121: 1)
  - Cabinet Council on Economic Affairs Working Group on Federal Credit Policy – September 18, 1981 (Box-folder 121: 2)
  - Cabinet Council on Economic Affairs Working Group on Federal Credit Policy – October 23, 1981 (Box-folder 121: 3)
  - (Box-folder 121: 4-5)
  - 1983 Credit Wrap Up (Box-folder 121: 6)
  - Federal Financing Bank (Box-folder 121: 7)
  - Federal Financing Bank (Box-folder 121: 8)
  - General File (Box-folder 121: 9)
  - Status of Remaining Administration Legislation (Box-folder 121: 10)
  - Patent User Fees Notes (Box-folder 121: 11)
  - Betamax Draft Notes (Box-folder 121: 12)
  - Correspondence (Box-folder 121: 13)
  - Gram/Latta Democrats (Box-folder 121: 14)
  - Travel and tourism – Early August 1981 (Box-folder 121: 15)
  - Illegal Immigration (Box-folder 122: 1)
  - New York Times articles (Box-folder 122: 2)
  - Position on Immigration Bill (Box-folder 122: 3)
  - Immigration (Box-folder 122: 4)
  - Washington Post articles (Box-folder 122: 5)
  - Statement regards to S. 2222 (Box-folder 122: 6)
  - New York Times article/Immigration Control (Box-folder 122: 7)
  - Intelligence on Immigration Bill (Box-folder 122: 8)
  - Current Information (Box-folder 122: 9)
  - Scorekeeping: Results of BRB and Presidential Appeals (Box-folder 122: 10)
  - Proposed Guidance on FY 83 Budget Issues (Box-folder 122: 11)
  - Constant Dollars and Current Dollars – Law Enforcement Resources (Box-folder 122: 12)
  - Documents on Domenici plan (Box-folder 122: 13)
  - Bill Status - Summary (Box-folder 122: 14)
  - Fiscal Year 1981 Department of Agriculture (Box-folder 122: 15)
  - Text of the Address by the President on the State of the Union – January 25, 1983 (Box-folder 122: 16)
  - Reconciliation Comparison – 1981 (Box-folder 122: 17)
  - House Budget Committee Reconciliation Table Revisions and Gram-Latta II Working Pages (Box-folder 122: 18)
  - Table of Contents – September 2, 1981 (Box-folder 122: 19)
  - Fiscal Year 1982 (Box-folder 122: 20)
  - Overview (Box-folder 122: 21)
  - Bill Introduction Status Report (Box-folder 122: 22)
  - Administration Cost-Saving Legislative Proposals (Box-folder 122: 23)
  - Fiscal Year 1981-Comparison of President Reagan March Revision and Chairman’s Recommendation Using HBC Economic Assumptions (Box-folder 122: 24)
  - Categories Presentation Control Sheet (Box-folder 122: 25)
  - Federal Credit Absorption (Box-folder 123: 1)
  - The Briefing Book for Credit Entitlement and Subsidies to Individuals (Box-folder 123: 2)
  - Federal Credit Management (Box-folder 123: 3)
  - FFB (Box-folder 123: 4)
  - Analysis of the Five Major Proposed Reductions ($20.3 Billion) (Box-folder 123: 5)
  - GNMA-FHA (Box-folder 123: 6)
  - Housing Affairs Letter – September 18, 1981 (Box-folder 123: 7)
  - Statements of Lawrence A. Kudlow (Box-folder 123: 8)
  - Federal Financing Bank (Box-folder 123: 9)
  - Federally Guaranteed Housing Credit, 1983 (Box-folder 123: 10)
  - TCH revised loan guarantee papers (Box-folder 123: 11)
  - Housing Issues and Recommendations for CCEA Credit Policy Working Group (Box-folder 123: 12)
  - Copies of permanent full-time positions and staff years for FHA all housing programs and all of HUD (Box-folder 123: 13)
  - The Proposed Privatization of FHLMC (Box-folder 123: 14)
  - Cabinet Council on Economic Affairs--September 23 Meeting (Box-folder 123: 15)
  - Invitation letter to Dr. Anderson to the public debut of Instead of Regulation (Box-folder 123: 16)
  - Federal Block Grants: The States’ Early Responses (Box-folder 123: 17)
  - Article in Housing Affairs Letter – trade association newsletter (Box-folder 123: 18)
  - Working Group Meeting – August 19, 1981 (Box-folder 123: 19)
  - Agricultural Briefing Materials (Box-folder 123: 20)
  - Proposed BRD Treatment of 1982 Loan Guarantee Limitations in 1983 Budget (Box-folder 123: 21)
  - Talking Points on FHA/GNMA for the Cabinet Council Meeting (Box-folder 123: 22)
  - Further Discussion of Housing Credit (Box-folder 123: 23)
  - Reductions in the 1983 FHA Commitment Limitation (Box-folder 123: 24)
  - 1982 Credit Limitation (Box-folder 123: 25)
  - Review book for Federally Assisted Housing Credit and a revised schedule for Working Group meetings (Box-folder 123: 26)
  - HUD Problems (Box-folder 123: 27)
  - HUD Problems (Box-folder 124: 1-2)
  - PMI Mortgage Corporation (Box-folder 124: 3)
  - Justice 1982 (Box-folder 124: 4-5)
  - Transportation Problems (Box-folder 124: 6)
  - Federal Credit Working Group Update (Box-folder 124: 7)
  - Federal Credit Budget Scorecard (Box-folder 124: 8)
  - Domestic Economic Policy (Box-folder 124: 9)
  - Cabinet Council on Economic Affairs—Meeting—June 22, 1982 (Box-folder 124: 10)
  - Direct and Guaranteed Loans for Business Outstanding June 30, 1981 (Box-folder 124: 11)
  - Credit Working Group Notes (Box-folder 124: 12)
  - Editorials from the Wall Street Journal (Box-folder 124: 13)
  - Reduction in 1982 New Commitments for Loan Guarantees (Box-folder 124: 14)
  - Cabinet Council on Economic Affairs – December 4 meeting (Box-folder 124: 15)
  - HUD Response to OMB Credit Reduction Proposals (Box-folder 124: 16)
  - Graduated Payment Mortgages (Box-folder 124: 17)
  - Proposed Loan Guarantee Target Letter to the Agencies (Box-folder 124: 18)
  - Washington Report – October 30, 1981 (Box-folder 124: 19)
  - Fact Sheet: Federal Credit/Loan Guarantee Reduction (Box-folder 124: 20)
  - Statement of Lawrence A. Kudlow – October 20, 1981 (Box-folder 124: 21)
  - Press Briefing by Larry Kudlow – November 5, 1981 (Box-folder 124: 22)
  - An Assessment of the Nation’s Housing Stock Problem and An Examination of the Households Income Eligible for Federal Housing Assistance (Box-folder 125: 1)
  - Formulation of the FY 1983 Credit Budget (Box-folder 125: 2)
  - Forecasts of FHA Insurance Activity (Box-folder 125: 3)
  - Credit/Credit Limitation (Box-folder 125: 4)
  - Business Tax Preferences Enacted as of December 31, 1980 (Box-folder 125: 5)
  - GNMA and 10-year Treasury bond yields (Box-folder 125: 6)
  - Legislation 1982 (Box-folder 125: 7)
  - Legislative Problems (Box-folder 125: 8)
  - Presidential Appointees (Box-folder 125: 9)
  - Leading Indicators in September (Box-folder 125: 10)
  - Economic Review/Economic Growth (Box-folder 125: 11-12)
  - Staff Meetings (Box-folder 125: 13)
  - Budget + Economy 1983 Summer (Box-folder 125: 14-15)
  - SBA Amendment (Box-folder 125: 16)
  - Gas Tax (Box-folder 126: 1)
  - Economic Assumptions for the Reagan Budget (Box-folder 126: 2)
  - Already-in-hand response notes/articles (Box-folder 126: 3)
  - Hoover Institution Fellows and Staff in Government Service (Box-folder 126: 4)
  - Appointment of Carey P. Modlin as Assistant Director for Budget Review (Box-folder 126: 5)
  - Appointments – March 18, 1981 (Box-folder 126: 6)
  - Memorandum to OMB Staff regarding appointment of James F. Kelly (Box-folder 126: 7)
  - Office of Press Secretary immediate releases (Box-folder 126: 8)
  - Monetary Trends – July 20, 1982 (Box-folder 126: 9)
  - Article: The Workaholic Boss: An 18-Hour-a-Day Menace (Box-folder 126: 10)
  - Cabinet Council on Economic Affairs – meeting – June 23, 1982 (Box-folder 126: 11)
  - Economic and Financial Update (Box-folder 126: 12)
  - T-1 Breakfast: Some Monetary Thoughts (Box-folder 126: 13)
  - U.S. Financial Data – Week ending July 28, 1982/August 4, 1982 (Box-folder 126: 14)
  - Economic Situation (Box-folder 126: 15)
  - Interest Rate Trends – August 18, 1982 (Box-folder 126: 16)
  - Business Credit Demand and Interest Rates (Box-folder 126: 17)
  - Federal Reserve Board Forecast (Box-folder 126: 18)
  - PLEV (Box-folder 126: 19-20)
  - Money Supply/Credit Market Report (Box-folder 126: 21)
  - E+G Airforce + Navy (Box-folder 126: 22)
  - Cabinet Council on Legal Policy (Box-folder 126: 23)
  - LRD (Box-folder 126: 24)
  - Small Business Bail-out Proposals (Box-folder 126: 25)
  - FEHB/Devine (Box-folder 126: 26)
  - Policy Meeting (Box-folder 126: 27)
  - Talking Points (Box-folder 126: 28)
  - Weekly Report/Wright (Box-folder 126: 29)
  - Property (Box-folder 126: 30-31)
  - Property (Box-folder 127: 1)
  - Appropriations September Exercise (Box-folder 127: 2)
  - Accounts Requiring Exceptions from Standard Treatment (Box-folder 127: 3-4)
  - Reconciliation by House Committee (Box-folder 127: 5)
  - Statement of Edwin L. Harper – June 18, 1981 (Box-folder 127: 6)
  - Governor’s Bulletin (Box-folder 127: 7)
  - International Security Studies Program – Number 20 Making the all-volunteer force work (Box-folder 127: 8)
  - IRC Amendments (Box-folder 127: 9)
  - Dave Stockman’s notes for his talk to the Council on Foreign Relations on May 20, 1981 (Box-folder 127: 10)
  - Preparing and Issuing OMB Directives (Box-folder 127: 11)
  - Juvenile Justice Fact Sheet – April 15, 1981 (Box-folder 127: 12)
  - Medical Services program of the Federal Prison System (Box-folder 127: 13)
  - Analysis of Hollings and Gram Proposals (Box-folder 127: 14)
  - Fed Breakfast, August 19 (Box-folder 127: 15)
  - Draft response to Congressman Gene Snyder (Box-folder 127: 16)
  - Interest Rate Control – Some Heretical Thoughts (Box-folder 127: 17)
  - Summaries of the recent CBO report (Box-folder 127: 18)
  - Retail Sales for August (Box-folder 127: 19)
  - CCEA minutes – September 9, 1982 (Box-folder 127: 20)
  - Housing starts in August – 1982 (Box-folder 127: 21)
  - Backup tables relating to the revised estimates of the budget resolution (Box-folder 127: 22)
  - Fact sheets on unemployment (Box-folder 127: 23)
  - Major Bills Enacted in the 97th Congress (Box-folder 127: 24)
  - Federal assistance for those in need of help (Box-folder 127: 25)
  - Memorandum for consumer prices in September (Box-folder 127: 26)
  - CCEA minutes of the September 29 and October 8 meetings – 1982 (Box-folder 127: 27)
  - OMB Central Budget Management System-Summary of three budget baseline versions – Nov. 5, 1982 (Box-folder 128: 1)
  - Economic Assumptions for the 1983 Budget (Box-folder 128: 2)
  - Summaries of final action on 1982 appropriation bills (Box-folder 128: 3)
  - OMB Central Budget Management System-Summary of three budget baseline versions – Nov. 4, 1982 (Box-folder 128: 4)
  - OMB Central Budget Management System-1984 Budget baselines: current services vs. October plan vs. agency request (Box-folder 128: 5)
  - Outstanding Budget Issues (Box-folder 128: 6)
  - Memorandum for status of budget appeals (Box-folder 128: 7)
  - Status of appeals to the budget review board – December 9, 1981 (Box-folder 128: 8)
  - Near final copies of the computer runs by category and sub-category (Box-folder 128: 9)
  - Revised Economic Assumptions for the 1983 Budget (Box-folder 128: 10)
  - Comments on Proposal on GAO Proposals Unpaid Taxes (Box-folder 128: 11)
  - Fiscal Year 1983 Budget Policy Wrap-Up (Box-folder 128: 12)
  - Economics and Government tables and notes (Box-folder 128: 13)
  - Open Issues for the 1983 Budget (Box-folder 128: 14)
  - 1984 Development (Box-folder 128: 15)
  - Federal Employment: Final Results (Box-folder 128: 16)
  - Scorekeeping Report (Box-folder 128: 17-18)
  - Agriculture and Related Agencies Accounts Reduced Below September Request 1 (Box-folder 128: 19)
  - Charts for DAS presentation (Box-folder 128: 20)
  - Quick turn-around exercise – December 6, 1981 (Box-folder 128: 21)
  - Pages of the Director’s presentation on appeals vs. overall picture on which TCH has additions or changes (Box-folder 128: 22)
  - Problems with the Alternate Continuing Resolution (Box-folder 128: 23)
  - Substitute Reconciliation Bill Savings (GL-11) – June 13, 1981 (Box-folder 128: 24)
  - Final Gramm-Latta II proposal estimates (Box-folder 128: 25)
  - Continuing Resolution Comparison – December 10, 1981 (Box-folder 128: 26)
  - Third Continuing Resolution – House appropriations Committee Action (Box-folder 128: 27)
  - DAS draft of part III (Box-folder 128: 28)
  - Scorekeeping Report (19)(30)(46) (Box-folder 129: 1)
  - U.S. General Accounting Office: Comments on the President’s February 18, 1981, Budget Proposals and Additional Cost-Saving Measures (Box-folder 129: 2)
  - Summary Fact Sheet-A program for economic recovery (Box-folder 129: 3)
  - Fact Sheet – President Reagan’s Initiative to Reduce Regulatory Burdens (Box-folder 129: 4)
  - The Reagan Economic Program: Selected Budget Cuts (Box-folder 129: 5)
  - Mid-session review of the 1982 budget (Box-folder 129: 6)
  - A Regional Analysis of the President’s Economic Recovery Program (Box-folder 129: 7)
  - Final version of the draft statement delivered to Cong. Latta – May 5 (Box-folder 129: 8)
  - Revision of Reconciliation Tables to Reflect Completed Senate Committee Action (Box-folder 129: 9)
  - 1983 Budget Justification Requirements (Box-folder 129: 10)
  - Reconciliation by House committee—totals – June 13, 1981 (Box-folder 129: 11)
  - Revision of Reconciliation Tables to Reflect Completed House Committee Action and Further Gramm-Latta II Decisions (Box-folder 129: 12)
  - Working Papers Gramm-Latta II package (Box-folder 129: 13)
  - Money Supply/Credit Market Reports (Box-folder 129: 14)
  - Memorandum for the status of loan guarantee reductions for 1982 (Box-folder 129: 15)
  - CCEA notes – October 5, 1982 (Box-folder 129: 16)